<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Podcasts on Hi, I&#39;m Irma.</title>
    <link>/podcast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Podcasts on Hi, I&#39;m Irma.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to become a better Product Manager in 2019 ft. Beau Blinder | S1, EP. 7</title>
      <link>/podcast/beau_blinder_s1ep7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcast/beau_blinder_s1ep7/</guid>
      <description>Our Guest On episode 7 of Elevatd Life, we have Beau Blinder. I found Beau after his post on Medium titled &amp;ldquo;3 Practical Ways To Become A Better Product Manager&amp;rdquo; and we were able to have a really insightful conversation about those 3 core ways he talked about in his post and how he’s proactively started to build a strong system to include Engineers in customer conversations which leads to building better products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Life of an IBM Product Manager ft. Zia Mohammad | S1, EP. 6</title>
      <link>/podcast/zia_mohammad_s1ep6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcast/zia_mohammad_s1ep6/</guid>
      <description>Our Guest On episode 6 of Elevatd Life, we have Zia Mohammad. Zia is a talented Product Manager at IBM working with the Watson Premium product. Zia was a delight to talk to - before starting at IBM he started gaining interest in technology through different news outlets that were showcasing all the amazing and innovative solutions AI and ML were allowing folks to do. He ended up going to school at Ohio State and then stumbled across an intern position at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Product Meets a Scientific Approach ft. Holly Hester-Reilly | S1, EP. 5</title>
      <link>/podcast/holly_hester_reilly_s1ep5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcast/holly_hester_reilly_s1ep5/</guid>
      <description>Our Guest On episode 4 of Elevatd Life, we have Brittany Cheng - Product Manager at Seesaw Learning (a platform for student engagement). Brittany grew up in the Bay area and has been surrounded by tech from childhood. She previously worked at Yelp focusing on the international product and search. She enjoys how Product Management allows her to connect the dots between people, data, ideas and users to solve challenges in the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iteration is Key ft. Brittany Cheng | S1, EP. 4</title>
      <link>/podcast/brittany_cheng_s1ep4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcast/brittany_cheng_s1ep4/</guid>
      <description>Our Guest On episode 5 of Elevatd Life, we have Holly Hester-Reilly. Holly is the Founder &amp;amp; CEO of H2R Product Science where she works with product leaders and teams to develop their product growth strategy. Holly majored in Chemical Engineering at Columbia University before realizing that she could apply her scientific research to help motivated teams build successful products. Outside of work, Holly focuses on parenting and geeking out at a local strategy game spot!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the Why ft. Zack Naylor | S1, EP. 3</title>
      <link>/podcast/zack_naylor_s1ep3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcast/zack_naylor_s1ep3/</guid>
      <description>Our Guest On episode 3 of Elevatd Life, we have Zack Naylor CEO and co-founder of Aurelius Lab a platform for tracking user research insights. He&amp;rsquo;s built a product-driven team from the ground up, comes from a heavy UX background is one of the first CEO&amp;rsquo;s that I&amp;rsquo;ve met that consistently interacts with users.
Our Highlights  How Zack started in UX and then went on to starting his own business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Rejection Turns into a Stunning Career ft. Morgan Meredith | S1, EP. 1</title>
      <link>/podcast/zack_naylor_s1ep4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcast/zack_naylor_s1ep4/</guid>
      <description>Our Guest On episode 1 of Elevatd Life, we have Morgan Meredith a Senior Release Manager at Jellyvision! This episode really dives in to how careers can take many twists and turns but at the end of the day if you keep working at your craft and constantly apply yourself you can jump and right where you want to be.
Morgan went from studying hearing science and sound acoustics to working at Yello in Chicago, IL and now leading the Release Management team at Jellyvision.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>