<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Hi, I&#39;m Irma.</title>
    <link>/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Hi, I&#39;m Irma.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HeyDay, a PoC Co-working App | No Code Build</title>
      <link>/work/building-a-people-of-color-coworking-app-with-no-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/building-a-people-of-color-coworking-app-with-no-code/</guid>
      <description>Introducing your POC co-working platform HeyDay is a passion project of mine. As a triple minority it can be nervewracking entering new spaces where I don&amp;rsquo;t see people that look like me.
So, HeyDay was born. I started to not only realize that finding safe spaces is difficult but I also realized that I needed more accountability for my scheduling and getting work done. It&amp;rsquo;s hard, right?
Days become short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TooBusy, a job site | No Code Build</title>
      <link>/work/building-a-job-site-for-underrepresented-folks-in-tech-with-no-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/building-a-job-site-for-underrepresented-folks-in-tech-with-no-code/</guid>
      <description>I started to reflect on my journey applying to jobs, interviewing, getting rejections and accepting offers. I came to understand that outside of being referred by a friend or a connection or being spammed by random recuriers trying to bring you on for a skill that&amp;rsquo;s not even on your LinkedIn profile, usually job seekers have will apply directly on the job posting.
So let&amp;rsquo;s think about this. A company, hiring manager or HR will draft up a job description with their &amp;ldquo;ideal&amp;rdquo; sometimes &amp;ldquo;perfect&amp;rdquo; candidate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onePodcast Weekly Newsletter | No Code Build</title>
      <link>/work/building-a-weekly-podcast-newsletter-with-no-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/building-a-weekly-podcast-newsletter-with-no-code/</guid>
      <description>Building a newsletter is easy, right? That’s subjective.
Over the last few weeks I’ve been on a mission. A mission to build. Build something, anything! I went back and forth with ideas I have jotted in my Notion.so app. Some solved problems others were just silly and fun so I had a great mix of varied ideas.
In the end, I settled on seeing and building out 2 ideas. This is the story about the first one, I’m calling her onePodcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FITTY, a Fitness App | Case Study</title>
      <link>/work/case-study-for-fitty-a-mobile-fitness-trainer-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/case-study-for-fitty-a-mobile-fitness-trainer-app/</guid>
      <description>FITTY is a mobile app specifically for personal fitness trainers. I went on the hunt for an app that allowed personal trainers to track, update, communicate and perform scheduling with their clients and the ones I found out there were abysmal. So, I thought — “What if I come up with my own?” And here we are today!
The Problem Fitness trainers, we love em’ or maybe we love to hate them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>