<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hi, I&#39;m Irma.</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hi, I&#39;m Irma.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Struggling with finding remote engineering roles? This can help.</title>
      <link>/blog/find-and-land-your-next-remote-engineering-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/find-and-land-your-next-remote-engineering-role/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be covering 2 big topics to help you find and land your next Remote Engineering role. The first is understanding how to best showcase that you&amp;rsquo;re open and ready to work in a remote work environment. Secondly, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you a few sites that have truly worked for friends in the past to find and at least get an interview for a remote role.
Building and starting to showcase your remote experience Here are few ways to spin remote work experience and showcase it if you&amp;rsquo;re applying for a job that requires remote experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>struggling with endless meetings?</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>So you’re having trouble with meetings, huh?
It’s a problem a lot of us have. I have yet to meet 1 person who has meetings, scheduling them, etc. to work perfectly. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly sometimes even worse in a remote setting because I can just pop over to your calendar and pick anytime I please to meet with you.
In the meantime, while that is being figured out, here is a great post by Flexiple on how you can schedule meetings like a BOSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways Rock Climbing Has Taught Me To Be A Better Product Manager</title>
      <link>/blog/3-ways-rock-climbing-has-taught-me-to-be-a-better-product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/3-ways-rock-climbing-has-taught-me-to-be-a-better-product-manager/</guid>
      <description>Rock climbing, it&amp;rsquo;s taught me a thing or two. There&amp;rsquo;s way more than I listed here as learnings but these are the top three ways I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to become a better Product Manager through learnings from rock climbing.
Trust In rock climbing, there are many instances where you&amp;rsquo;re faced with a choice. A choice to trust or not to trust. Of course, the choice you make has its own consequences but 1 gets you a little further than the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>building (a weekly podcast newsletter) in 48 hours with no-code</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>Building a newsletter is easy, right? That’s subjective.
Over the last few weeks I’ve been on a mission. A mission to build. Build something, anything! I went back and forth with ideas I have jotted in my Notion.so app. Some solved problems others were just silly and fun so I had a great mix of varied ideas.
In the end, I settled on seeing and building out 2 ideas. This is the story about the first one, I’m calling her onePodcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weekly digest 4 - getting better with deep focus</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another Weekly Digest, #4 that is! Crazy, we are already at 4. As usual, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a few jobs for you to peek at, product of the week and my biggest learning from this week.
Jobs! 🔥 Lead Software Engineer @ StitchFix - click here
 Team size: medium | Location: ✈️ Remote  Senior Product Analyst @ Coffee Meets Bagel - click here
 Team size: medium | Location: SF, Seattle, or Remote  Full-Stack Developer @ Peer Grade - click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weekly digest 3 - move quickly and safely</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>Another Weekly Digest, #3 this time. As usual, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a few jobs for you to peek at, product of the week and my biggest learning from this week.
Jobs! 🔥 Program Manager, Transportation @ Amazon - click here
 Team size: large | Location: ✈️ Remote  Project Manager @ Pixel Cabin - click here
 Team size: small | Location: ✈️ Remote  Backend Engineer @ Flickr - click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weekly digest 2 - jobs, thoughts, opinions delivered</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>Rolling out Weekly Digest #2. As usual, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a few jobs for you to peek at, product of the week and my biggest learning from this week.
Jobs! 🔥 Site Reliability Engineer @ Peloton - click here
 Team size: medium | Location: ✈️ Remote or NY  Customer Success Specialist @ Raisely - click here
 Team size: small | Location: ✈️ Remote  Customer Technical Support Specialist @ Market Muscles - click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weekly digest 1 - hello, 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m starting a Weekly Digest! What does that mean? I&amp;rsquo;ll be summarizing few jobs for you to peek at, product of the week and my biggest learning from this week.
Jobs! 🔥 Senior Data Product Manager @ The Democratic National Committee - click here
 Team size: small | Location: ✈️ Remote  Engineering Manager @ Auth0 - click here
 Team size: medium | Location: ✈️ Remote  Product Designer (UI/UX) @ Treehouse - click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>empowering your Engineering teams</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>I’ve received 1:1 messages from engineers asking if they can go into our project management tool and enter in a task. Of course, I say “yes” and also remind them to enter tasks in immediately if it’ll help them unblock their work. This is one way we can empower engineering teams to perform autonomously.
As a Dev Manager, Scrum Master, Product Manager &amp;amp; CTO (I know, there are a few more roles I’m missing) actively practicing ways to build trust and confidence in your engineers is crucial to the health of your team as well as the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grow your skillsets with side projects</title>
      <link>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creation-dun-nouveau-theme/</guid>
      <description>Let me start with this: props to the person who submitted this question on #AskWiP! It’s a question that many have when they’re starting to build product skills and for good reason — open source product management opportunities are difficult to find. Unlike software engineering, where you’ll find Github projects or non-profit organizations actively looking for volunteers at any level to come on board and contribute, open source projects that look for volunteer PMs are almost non-existent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>